## **Muhammad Umer Iftikhar**

House No. 59

Bilal Street, Phase-I, Khyaban-e-Sadiq

Sargodha, Pakistan

Mobile: +92-300-9601954

E-mail: m.umeriftikhar@gmail.com

D.O.B: 06-April-1984

# **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

With immense passion towards the field of education and training and having gained thorough expertise in all the concepts and theories of accounting, business and finance, looking forward to similar job opportunities in renowned institutions, where not just theoretical but practical knowledge is also given due importance.

# **EDUCATION**

#### The University of Lahore, Lahore, Pakistan

Master of Philosophy in Management Sciences, Finance with 3.28 (2013-2016)

# **Coventry University, Coventry, United Kingdom**

MBA (Banking and Finance), With Merit, 66% (2009-2010)

# Kaplan Financial, London, United Kingdom

Association of Chartered Certified Accountants (2007-2010) ACCA Fundamental Level, August 2009

ACCA Professional Level, August 2010

## Oxford Brookes University, Oxford, United Kingdom

BSc (Hons) in Applied Accounting, 2:1 (2007-2010)

## SKANS School of Accountancy, Lahore, Pakistan

Certified Accounting Technician, (2002-2004)

#### Air Base Inter College Sargodha, Sargodha, Pakistan

Higher Secondary School Certificate, 69 % (2000-2002)

#### Air Base Inter College Sargodha, Sargodha, Pakistan

Secondary School Certificate, 73.52 % (1998-2000)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **A**CADEMIC **E**XPERIENCE:

## University of Sargodha, Sub Campus Bhakkar, Pakistan

Lecturer BS-18 (contract basis), Commerce Department, Sep. 2011- Present



# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:

# Bahria Town-DBH-JV Project Islamabad, Pakistan

Internal Auditor, Apr,2011-Sept,2011

Duties: Audit of all account matters, Audit of stores, payroll, procurement and human resource.

## **Blagreaves Veterinary Centre, Derby, United Kingdom**

Accounts Assistant, Mar, 2009-Jan, 2011

Duties: Book keeping and preparation of Final Accounts.

## Yussouf & CO, London, United Kingdom

Accounts/Audit Trainee, July,2007-Feb,2009

Duties: Preparation of VAT/Tax returns, bank reconciliations, control accounts, trial balance and final accounts.

# **REFERENCES**

• Will be furnished upon request.